Record Industry Publicity Collection
Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division, Library of Congress
- Series 13. Radio Companies, 1944-1946, and undated, .25 linear feet
  - For Release, 1946, Benton & Bowles, Inc. (Box-folder 41/9)
  - Music of the Jazz Bands continuity, [U.S. Office of War Information?], Overseas Distribution Section
    - No. 53, circa 1945 (Box-folder 41/10)
    - No. 54, circa mid 1940s (Box-folder 41/11)
  - Music of the Theatre, nos. 49-50, undated, [U.S. Office of War Information?], Radio Outpost Division (Box-folder 41/12)
  - Outpost Concert Series, no. 28, undated, [U.S. Office of War Information?], Radio Outpost Division (Box-folder 41/13)
  - Radio Symphonies of America, nos. 35-37, 46, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 41/14)
- Series 14. Concert and Festival Programs and Announcements, 1944-1956, .1 linear feet (Box-folder 41/15)
  Consists of announcements, fliers, and releases about concerts and festivals.